[{"answer": "Very good.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How are you both?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Do you feel like you've been to the lion's den a bit tonight?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I always get nervous in interviews, especially being on CNN.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Because it's just, you know, a very serious place and you make me nervous.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Why CNN?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I would.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Would you like to be taken more seriously?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Because I feel like I've really grown in the past couple of years, I just turned 30, I'm an adult, and I feel that I deserve it.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Why would you care about being taken seriously?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "It was exciting.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "How did it make you feel?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "She can be.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Are you saying Paris is shy?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "You can be shy?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Because I missed you.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What place do you need to be?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I'm here for \"The World According To Paris,\" which is my new TV show.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What are you promoting?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Very.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "How interested are you in the world?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Are you interested in world affairs?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Genuinely?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, I have so much going on in my life.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "When you see what's going on in the Middle East and stuff like that, do you have a -- do you have a healthy interest or does that kind of stuff not really touch your life?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "It's been quite an experience.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What's it like being Paris Hilton's mom?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "You know, it used to really bother me when I first came out in the media when I was 15 years old.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Are you happy with that relationship with the media?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Do you Google yourself?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Singing.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "If you -- if you came on \"America's Got Talent,\" what would your -- what would your talent be?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "It's just part of my brand.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Are you getting you're a serious singer or are you a brand singer, as an extension of your brand?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "I mean, Kathy, what do you think of modern fame in that sense, that you can actually see your daughter, Paris, not going through a conventional talent like acting or any of those kind of things, but just being Paris Hilton and making all this money?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I used to but I really don't as much anymore.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Do you worry about her?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "She's behaving better and she's grown up and she's been through a lot.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Because she's behaving better?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "But you're aware you become an adult at 18?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "I think that, you know, she has a famous last name.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Why are people so fascinated by Paris, do you think?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "She didn't have to.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "And a lot of people look at her and say, well, why does she have to go and do anything?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "This show is all real, everything that happens and it was like I was finally ready to show who I really was and I'm really honest in the show.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Is this show that we're now going to see more of the real Paris do you think?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Oh, I think there's definitely a lot, just having the last name Hilton, people assume that everything was handed to me and I've never had to work a day in my life.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What are the misconceptions about you?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Just growing up my parents never spoiled us.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "How much of that goes down to your parents?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Family.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Family?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I was in shock.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "How did you actually feel?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Did you call your mum?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "You know, I don't.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Do you remember, Kathy?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "We had therapy and I think that that really helped.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "How did you get her back on track?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I didn't know what to say.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What can you say?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "I just -- just felt so betrayed.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What do you feel about them now?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I thought I did and I can't believe that he would do something like that to me.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "That you loved?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Do you have a tissue?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "No, it's OK, just --", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Do you want to take a little break?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "He was furious.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "When this whole tape thing blew up, what did Donald Trump say to you?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Dad and I talked with him mostly.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Did he give any advice on how to deal with it?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I've been doing this for 15 years now, so half of my life and there's it's up and downs.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "What do you think of the whole fame game now that you've had enough time to be in it for a while?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "One of the things is in the media, there's all these people who I've never met before, or maybe people from my past who want to sell stories and make money, so they'll make up these crazy stories and people believe them.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "What are those things that you wish you didn't have to put up with, other than what we've just discussed?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Well, when you're in this business, this is what you sign up for.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Are you really entitled to any privacy given the amount of your private life that you put out there for commercial gain?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Is that a price worth paying, in the end?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "She was a tomboy.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I think it has a lot to do with your family.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What do you think is behind that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Do you think you were?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, it was my first child, and I thought this is, you know, my little China cup.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Deliberately, do you think?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Well, there was not a kinder, more generous, loving, sweet, smart, smart -- I can't -- the most wonderful father.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What were the misconceptions about Michael, do you think?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I had just come back to the hotel.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Where were you when you heard he died?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "My assistant told me.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "The children and Mrs. Jackson and all the brothers and sisters and just everybody was in this room.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What was the scene there?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Did you say anything?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "And he was so fabulous at the hotel.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Incredibly sad end to his life, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Yeah, I grew up -- just my mom -- I remember -- one of the first memories I have of him was when my mom took us to the music video set of \"Thriller.\"", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Paris, did you know Michael well?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I was honored.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "You know, Latoya will tell you the story.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Was it a direct result?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I saw them a couple weeks ago.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Have you seen the children much since he died?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you that when he was at the Bel Air Hotel, there was none -- there was none of that.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Is that an inaccurate portrayal, do you think?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, I think that now that he's gone, everybody realizes what a good person, all the wonderful things that he's done for charity.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What do you think his legacy will be, Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I have 17 different product lines.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "How many current businesses do you have?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I don't think you know that part.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Do you keep a handle on it?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "I would imagine it's more than that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "I do very well for myself.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Is it a lot more?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Fashion, fun, excitement, and amazing products.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "If you were pitching it to me, what do you personify?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "That I bet she does.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Do you keep a close eye on the money?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Don't to every what's this -- what's this --", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "It's about someone who has their own thing going on.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "How do you trust men?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Over a year now.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "You've been with him a couple years?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "I've never been happier.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Is this true love?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "We'll see what happens.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Think we may be seeing some real wedding bells soon?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "You know, I would love to have a family and children in the next couple of years, definitely.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Could you imagine being 35 and not married?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Do you think he's the one?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Paris, what 37,000 things are you up to?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Around the world.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I think Donald is a brand.", "docId": "110605pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Is that the game plan?", "qSentId": 662}]